目 前 資 金
最 新 余 額
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
打工
姐妹花
第十一集
第三季
打工
姐妹花
第十一集
第三季
翻校  我是男的賽太公
翻校  沒欺負人YY貓
后期  灰灰是菇涼
時間軸 總監  沒欺負人YY貓
停止計時
And, time.
37分鐘
37 minutes,
從家里出發  到坐上地鐵
we got from the apartment to the subway,
最后到達學校  又刷新記錄了
to the pastery school in record time.
雖然我來不及穿胸罩
I mean, I'm not wearing a bra,
而且丁字褲好像也前后穿反了
and my thong might be on backwards.
丁字褲怎么會穿反呢
There is no wrong way to wear a thong,
只要不舒服就對了
as long as it's uncomfortable.
而且你穿胸罩也只是擺設而已
And with you, the bra is just for decoration.
而我是必須得穿
I have to wear one because you get a ticket
"孩子"不放安全座椅上  是要吃罰單的
for not put the kids in a car seat.
教室見  我得先跟我老婆道別
See you in class guys, I gotta say good bye to my wife.
你真以為我要跟你吻別嗎
You think I was gonna kiss you?
對啊
Yes.
我是你老婆  你是我那位
I'm the wife, you are the husband
某天被我發現你有異裝癖
who I caught wearing my cloth one day,
但我卻沒戳穿的老公
but I don't say anything about it.
早安啊  二位
Morning, guys.
早安  碧碧
Oh, hi, Bebe.
見到我很驚訝吧
Surprised to see me, right?
大家總以為我會在夜半時分自殺
Everyone always thinks I'm not gonna make it through the night,
但我還活著  連我自己都驚訝
but here I am, even surprised myself.
跟一個隨時會崩潰的人
What's it like working in an office
在同一間辦公室工作是什么感覺呢
with someone who's about to snap like a breadstick?
絕對沒想象中這么有趣
Not as much fun as you'd think.
但碧碧人很好  而且在這工作
But Bebe's sweet, and working here
主要是為了替你掙學費
is putting you through pastry school.
-好啦  再見  -再見
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
-我要離婚  -早去申請了
- I want a divorce. - I already filed.
老婆  我要五塊錢
Hey, wife, I need $5
賠昨天弄壞的工具
to pay for a spatula I broke yesterday.
我昨天突然戈登﹒拉姆齊上身了
I was having a Gordon Ramsay moment.
戈登﹒拉姆齊  英國知名廚師與電視名人
脾氣火爆  時常罵人
有機會我不介意跟他睡哦
I'd have sex with him, by the way.
為啥  他肯定也是會吼你
Why? He'd just be yelling at you
然后說你"做"錯了
and telling you you're doing it wrong.
做愛不都這樣嗎
Yeah, sex.
拿吧  錢在我包里
Take it. It's in my purse.
碧碧  你有偷偷不吃的藥嗎
Yo, Bebe, you got any extra pills you're not taking?
沒有  我全都有吃
No, I'm taking them all.
老天爺  別啊
Oh, my God, no.
干嘛  我也就想要個一顆  兩顆
What? I just wanted one. Or two.
就想減減壓
Just to take the edge off.
三點我有一場生奶油考試
I have a whipped cream final at 3:00.
是報紙里的訃告
No. In the obituaries.
我認識這個人
I know this person.
"安東尼婭﹒佛羅倫蒂諾  享年八十
"Antonia Florentino, 80,
在睡夢中安詳過世"
Died peacefully in her sleep."
明顯是自殺嘛  對吧
That's a suicide, right?
她是我的保姆
She was my nanny.
你現在還有保姆啊
You still have a nanny?
真幸福
Lucky.
我小時候大多數時間都是她帶大的
She took care of me most of my childhood.
我好愛她
I loved her so much.
節哀
So sorry.
我對我的老鄰居卡拉
That's kind of how I felt
也有這種感覺
about my old neighbor, Carla.
雖然她沒有養育我
I mean, she didn't take care of me,
但在我小的時候  她都允許我
but when I was a kid, she used to let me
喝她家花園水管的水
drink out of her hose.
我最后一次見安東尼婭  是她載我
The last time I saw Antonia, she was driving me
和邋遢鬼妮莉﹒費塔朵一起去參加青少年選擇獎
and a sloppy Nelly Furtado to the Teen Choice Awards.
妮莉﹒費塔朵加拿大女歌手  曾贏得過青少年選擇獎
現在可以在辦公室里哭了嗎
Oh, are we allowed to cry at work now?
我一般只在車里哭
'cause I only do it in my car.
麥克斯  你知道我意識到什么嗎
Max, you know what I just realized?
這是我保姆死后  我第一次走進這家餐廳
This is the first time I've been here since my nanny died.
這話你已經在墨西哥快餐店說過了
You just said that at Chipotle.
然后十分鐘后  你又說了一遍
And then you said it again ten minutes later,
也是在那家快餐店
also at chipotle.
有點同情心好嗎
Show some sensitivity.
我當時哭是因為我保姆死了
I was crying because my nanny died.
也因為我們悼念的早午餐是在一家快餐店
And also because our grief brunch was at Chipotle.
卡洛琳  你的保姆過世啦
Caroline, your nanny passed?
我深表同情  寶貝  太遺憾了
My sympathies, sweetheart. That's a shame.
但沒有什么比黑人葬禮更棒的了
But there is nothing better than a black funeral.
我1984年時參加了我爺爺的葬禮  至今宿醉未醒
I'm still hung over from my grandpa's in '84.
厄爾  我的保姆是白人
Earl, my nanny was white.
你的保姆居然是白人
Your nanny was white?
小姑娘  你的確是富二代啊
Child, you were rich.
你看見阿憨了嗎
Have you seen Han?
葬禮明天在費城舉行
The funeral's in Philadelphia tomorrow,
我得跟他請一天假
and I need the day off.
我之前好像看見他了
Well, I think I saw him earlier.
但話說回來  那也有可能是一只貓
But then again, it might have been a cat.
我們倆都需要請一天假
Hey, we both need the day off.
我要陪你去  無論是出于精神支持
I'm going with you for moral support/
還是為了吃第一個費城牛肉三明治
my first cheesesteak/
或我想使勁甩獨立鐘里面的那個大球
I want to ride the liberty bell like a wrecking ball.
我剛在《科技新時代》看到一篇超級瘋狂的文章
I just read the craziest article in this Popular Science
是關于"白矮"星  黑"洞"和天王星[你屁眼]
about White Dwarfs, black holes, and Uranus.
不對  讓我重新說一遍
Oh, no. Let me start over.
阿憨  我們明天要請假  我保姆過世了
Han, we need tomorrow off. My nanny died.
她就像是我的母親
She was like a mother to me.
但她不是你的母親
But she was not your mother.
餐廳有明確的規定
And diner rules clearly state
必須是自己家人的葬禮才能請假
you can only take off for the death of a family member.
餐廳還規定不許在上班時候喝酒呢
Well, the rules also say no drinking on the job,
但現在
but...
好吧  你可以去
Okay, yes, you can go.
因為在我們國家
Because in my culture,
對長輩是十分尊敬的
it's important to honor the elderly.
我跟一位97的老人同睡上下鋪
I shared a bunk bed with a 97-year-old
一直睡到我22歲呢
till I was 22.
敢問你是在"上面"還是"下面"
Were you on the top or bottom?
我向來是在下面啊
Oh, I was always the bottom.
不對  讓我重新說一遍
Oh, no. Let me start over.
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
我收到你保姆過世的短信了
I got your nanny death text.
所以我出于尊重  穿上了一身黑
So I'm wearing black out of respect.
而且  剛好我的月事也來了
And also, I got my period.
謝謝  蘇菲  太有愛了
Thanks, Sophie. That's lovely.
是嗎  哪部分
It is? Which part?
在波蘭  我保姆死的時候
You know, back in Poland when my nanny died,
我心都碎了  難過得都吃不下她了
I was so heartbroken, I could barely eat her.
你居然吃你死掉的保姆
You ate your dead nanny?
山羊終究是動物
Well, a goat's a goat.
稱呼改變不了本質
It doesn't matter what you name it.
它仍是美味的羊肉
It's still good goat meat.
好了  我去我卡座里坐著了
All right, I'll be in my booth.
一份金槍魚三明治和三顆痛經藥  謝謝
I'm going to order a tuna melt and three Midol, please.
等等  我們要怎么去費城啊
Wait, how are we gonna get there?
碧碧說她有車  我們可以問問她
Oh, Bebe said she had a car, we can just ask her.
我不想跟她坐同一輛車
I don't want to get in a car with her.
我連跟她說話都不想
I don't even want to get in a conversation with her.
我可以載你們去
I can drive you.
但我們得先去我巴克斯縣的姐姐家
We just have to stop at my sister's in Bucks County,
拿一個沒有任何標記的包裹
pick up an unmarked package,
然后再送到康乃迪克州
and swing by Connecticut to drop it off.
奧列格  這個包裹里有違法的東西嗎
Oleg, is there anything illegal about this delivery?
沒有  只是几雙鞋
No, it's just some shoes...
里面塞滿可卡因而已
stuffed with cocaine.
對了  鞋子是用印度大麻做的哦
Also the shoes are made of hashish.
我還是打給碧碧好了
I'll call Bebe.
好吧  但我要坐后座
Okay, but I'm sitting in the back
因為我不想沾染到她的瘋氣
'cause I don't want the crazy to get on me.
碧碧  你送我們去葬禮
Bebe, I can't thank you enough
真是太感謝你了
for driving us to the funeral.
現在車速才20邁  其實你可以開快點的
We're only going 20. You can go faster if you want.
是啊  剛有一棵樹超過了我們
Yeah, we just got passed by a tree.
你那只愛放屁和神經緊張的可卡犬
And I'm especially thrilled your nervous cocker spaniel
也跟著來  真讓我尤為振奮
with gas and hot spots got to join us.
夠了  你現在都開到100邁了
Okay, now you're going 100.
其實你可以開慢點的
We can go slower if you want.
抱歉  我的專長是做事極端
Sorry. Extremes-- that's my thing.
有一次我搬家到東京住了一天
One time I moved to Tokyo for a day.
-麥克斯  又來了  -我知道
- Max, it just hit me again. - I know.
貌似她給那只狗吃了西蘭花
It's like she feeds him broccoli.
不是啦
No.
是我又想到安東尼婭真的去世了
That Antonia is really dead.
好消息是  根據點評網
Well, the good news is, according to Yelp,
她葬禮距離最出名的那家
she's dead about two blocks
費城牛肉奶酪三明治只有兩個街區
From the famous philly cheesesteak place.
麥克斯  放尊重點行嗎
Max, show some respect.
我又不認識她
Well, I didn't know her.
老實說  我只當她是幫我和牛肉三明治
In fact, I only know her as the lady who brought me
牽紅線的媒人
and cheesesteaks together.
即使我們從未見過面  但對于安東尼婭的家人來說
Even though we've never met, it'll mean so much
我的出席對他們來說意義重大
to Antonia's family that I came out of respect.
對我的心理醫生來說也意義重大
It'll mean so much to my therapist
因為我離開我的安全區
that I left my safe zone
還只帶了一條狗
and only brought one of the dogs.
麥克斯  你覺得除了我的悼詞之外
Max, do you think in addition to my eulogy,
我還應該念几段我兒時的日記嗎
I should read something from my childhood journal?
不應該  但我覺得你還是會執意念
I don't, but I think you're gonna do it anyway.
"1997年  聖誕節早上
"Christmas morning, 1997.
安東尼婭用一杯熱可可和一根我最愛的
Antonia woke me up with a cup of hot cocoa
薄荷棒棒糖叫醒我
and my favorite peppermint stick,
然后我們開始拆禮物"
and then we opened presents."
1997年  聖誕節早上
Christmas morning, 1997.
我沖我媽臉上潑了一杯冰水
I threw cold water on my mother's face.
直到元旦那天  她人還是沒反應
New year's day-- still no movement.
這是我手上唯一一張我們的合影
This is the only picture I still have of us.
那是我們一起過的第一個萬聖節
It was our first Halloween together.
我當時四歲
I was four.
瞧她給我做的那身可愛的小雞裝束
Look at that cute little baby chick costume she made me.
唧唧  唧唧
Peep, peep.
真可愛
Aw, so cute.
看車
Car.
我從來沒穿過萬聖節服裝
I never had a Halloween costume.
我通常是把頭發亂糟糟地扎起來
I used to put my hair in a messy bun
然后跌跌撞撞地挨家挨戶敲門
and stumble from door-to-door
告訴大家我就是我媽
telling people I was my mother.
今年萬聖節  我打扮成我的醫生邁克
This Halloween, I went as my doctor, Michael.
我把我的狗狗打扮成
And I dressed up my buddy here
他的愛人  約瑟夫
As his lover, Joseph.
我們后來情不自禁
We lost.
安東尼婭一直陪在我身邊
Antonia was always there for me--
萬聖節  聖誕節  復活節  每一個節日
Halloween, Christmas, Easter-- every holiday.
每一天
Really, every day.
她就像我媽媽一樣
She was really like a mother to me.
那你真正的媽媽呢
Where was your real mother?
這只是什么品種的狗啊
Hey, what kind of dog is that?
除了"苦瓜臉品種"外
I mean, besides "Sad"?
她媽媽跟人偷情  然后被掃地出門
Her mother had an affair, got pushed out.
那是她的痛處  所以別隨便碰
That's her hot spot, so don't lick it.
沒關系  麥克斯  我不需要任何保護
It's okay, Max, I don't need any protection.
你不需要任何保護[措施]
You don't need protection?
你是誰  跟我約過會的男人嗎
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
碧碧  沒錯  我媽媽是背叛了我爸爸
Bebe, yes, my mother was unfaithful to my father,
所以她被趕走了
so she was sent away.
但我有安東尼婭  她照顧我
But I had Antonia and she took care of me.
她就是我的家人
She was my family.
那一定很難熬  人人都需要媽媽
That must have been hard. Everybody needs a mother.
我沒有我媽  一定會瘋掉的
I'd be crazy without my mother.
我看病都是她載我去的
She drives me to all my appointments.
但你不是會開車嗎
But you drive.
是啊
Yeah...
但醫生不讓我開
But I'm not supposed to.
我讓碧碧在車里等著沒事吧
It's okay I asked Bebe to wait in the car, right?
她不會憋死的  有扇車窗留了一條縫
I mean, she'll be okay. We cracked a window.
是啊  她有個碗和一個寵物用咀嚼玩具
Yeah, and she's got a bowl and a chew-toy.
來吧  過來簽到
Come on, let's sign in.
麥克斯  當我見到她家人時  我要振作
Max, I have to keep it together when I meet the family.
我不能太動情
I can't be all emotional.
瞧  我的手在抖  太可怕了
Look, my hand's shaking. This is terrible.
干嘛  剛才的簽名丑死了
What? It was a terrible signature.
而且那頁也只有五個其他人的名字而已
And there were only five other names on the page.
處理掉它
Get rid of it.
"處理掉它"
"Get rid of it"?
你是誰  跟我約過會的男人嗎
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
"卡洛琳﹒錢寧"
"Caroline Channing."
給  麥克斯
Here, Max.
瞧
Oh, look.
這里的花和一切都好美
The flowers and everything are so beautiful.
好了
There you go.
你居然簽"費成﹒三明智"
You signed "Phil E. Cheesesteak"?
你告訴我不要再提這件事了
You told me not to mention it anymore,
所以那只是個提醒而已
so it's just a reminder.
麥克斯  到時候一定會有很多人
Okay, Max, there are gonna be a lot of people
想要得到我的關注  所以拜托要耐心
who will want my attention, so please be patient
站在我身邊  偶爾給我支持的依靠
and stand next to me for the occasional supportive lean.
如果有人開始哭得太夸張
And if someone starts to get too weepy,
立刻把他們從我身上拉開
push them out of the way
因為這條裙子可不能沾上眼淚
because I can't get tears on this dress.
我明天九點前還得退給百貨公司
It has to be back to Barneys by 9:00 A.M.
你來了
You're here.
開始了  麥克斯
Here we go, Max.
我剛是跟他說話
I was talking to him.
當然當然  今天對我們來說都很傷心
Of course you were. It's a very sad day for us all.
真是太傷了
That was rough.
麥克斯  看
Max, look.
這就是安東尼婭
This is Antonia.
她看起來人很好
She looks really nice.
的確
She was.
原來她還在軍隊待過
I didn't know she was in the military.
美軍規定床單要掖進床墊下  四個角要折成45度
難怪床單四個邊角弄得那么利落
But it does explain those fabulous bed sheet corners.
等等  你居然不知道你的保姆是海軍嗎
Wait, you didn't know your nanny was a marine?
真是太糟糕了  如果是我就會炫耀
That's too bad, 'cause I'd be all,
"喂  其他有錢的小屁孩
"Yo, other little rich kid!
老娘的保姆能輕易折斷你們脖子哦"
My nanny can snap your neck."
瞧  那倆是她的姐妹  塞西莉亞和安吉拉
Oh, look. There are her sisters, Cecelia and Angela,
這几個是她的侄子和侄女
and there are her nieces and nephews.
這些照片居然沒一張有我
And there is not me anywhere.
我的照片肯定跟其他重要人物
You know, my picture must be in the coffin
一起放在棺材里
With the other V.I.P.S.
如果你是個重要人物  能叫人上酒嗎
If you're a V.I.P., can we get some bottle service?
下午好  女士們
Good afternoon, ladies.
我是安東尼  安東尼婭的侄子
I'm Anthony, Antonia's nephew.
真是令人難過的一天
It's sad day, huh?
沒錯
Yes, it is.
我覺得我現在也沒這么難過了
Think I just got a little less sad.
安東尼
Oh! Anthony!
住手  我們可是一家人
Stop. We're family.
我是卡洛琳﹒錢寧
I'm Caroline Channing.
我只知道你是卡洛琳辣妹
You're Caroline "Hot," is all I know.
你們倆是要用信封裝錢
You ladies need cash envelopes
還是要不要都行
or you guys cool?
我最缺的就是裝錢的信封了
I always need a cash envelope.
抱歉  信封要拿來裝什么啊
I'm sorry, envelopes for what?
根據意大利葬禮的習俗  哀悼者瞻仰死者遺容后
Well, at Italian wakes, the mourners give the family
會捐一點錢給死者家屬
a donation after they view the deceased.
所以是要"按次收費"瞻仰嗎
So it's pay-per-view?
這句吐槽太犀利了
That was a good one.
晚點要一起喝一杯嗎
Hey, you want to go get a pop later?
我們完事就走了  但好吧  安東尼
We're leaving right after, but yes, Anthony.
謝謝  麻煩給我們個信封
Thank you. We'll take an envelope.
遺體就在前面
The body's right through there.
一直往前走
Go right ahead.
安東尼  住手
Anthony, stop.
我真的好緊張啊
I'm really nervous.
我以前從來沒見過尸體
I've never seen a dead body before.
我見多了
I've seen a bunch.
有几具還是拜我所賜
A couple of them were my fault.
我沒有現金
I don't have any cash.
-你有帶錢嗎  -我看看我的錢包
- Do you have any money? - Let me check my wallet.
這是名牌密封塑膠袋  可不是什么山寨貨哦
This is a real Ziploc, not one of those knock-offs.
一定要把信封封好
Make sure you seal the envelope,
好讓別人覺得里面都是25美分的硬幣
so people think it's all quarters.
麥克斯  下一個到我們了
Max, we're next.
我好害怕  牽住我的手
I'm afraid. Hold my hand.
牽手  你以為我們是什么
Hold hands? What are we?
基督徒約會網站上第五次約會的男女嗎
On a ChristianMingle fifth date?
該網站是最大的信仰性在線約會網站之一
拜托了  麥克斯  我好緊張啊
Please, Max. I'm nervous.
-天啊  -謝謝
- Oh, God. - Thank you.
好了  松手
Okay. Now give it back.
干嘛  這已經是我維持最長的一段感情了
What? That was just my longest relationship.
再說了  我得把這些零錢放進信封里
Plus, I need it to put this change in the envelope.
她看起來一臉平靜
Oh, she looks so peaceful.
安東尼婭  我是卡洛琳
Hi, Antonia. It's me, Caroline.
我應該親她嗎  她家人在旁邊看著呢
Should I kiss her? The family is right there watching.
前面那個女士就親了
The lady before us kissed her.
親吧  反正看樣子她也不會推開你
Go for it. Doesn't look like she'd fight you.
好的  數到三
Okay, on the count of three.
一  二
One, two--
不行  麥克斯  牽著我的手
No! Max, hold my hand again while I--
我們該怎么辦
What do we do?
住手  別撿了  反正我們也要給她家人的
Wait, leave it! We were giving it to them anyway.
不是全部都給啊  那可是我們買三明治的錢
Not all of it. That's our cheesesteak money.
別撿了  快過來
Leave it. Come on.
剛才的事真是非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry about that.
我實在是太緊張了  你懂的
My nerves got the best of me. You understand.
我是塞西莉亞  安東尼婭的
I'm Cecelia, Antonia's--
妹妹  我知道
Sister. I know.
你們倆長得很像
I see the resemblance.
我是卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
誰啊  卡洛琳
Caroline who?
卡洛琳﹒錢寧啊
Oh. Caroline Channing.
誰是卡洛琳﹒錢寧
Caroline Channing who?
你現在心情不好想不起  可以理解
You're having a hard time processing. Understandable.
今天對我們所有人來說都非常難過
It's been a very emotional day for us all.
這個女孩是誰
Who is this girl?
你  我倒覺得我在哪里見過你
You, I feel like I've seen somewhere.
你是里基在羅徹斯特的女友嗎
Are you Ricky's girl From Rochester?
有可能  是的話對我有什么好處
I could be. What's in it for me?
安東尼婭在我小時候照顧過我
Antonia used to take care of me when I was little.
安東尼婭是你的臨時保姆啊
Oh, Antonia was your baby-sitter.
你能來真好
Very nice of you to come.
她不是我的"臨時保姆"
Well, she was hardly my "baby-sitter."
她十年來的每一天都在照顧我
She took care of me every day for ten years.
我是卡洛琳  卡洛琳﹒錢寧啊
Caroline. Caroline Channing.
很抱歉  但我真不認識你  親愛的
I'm sorry, but I don't know who you are, sweetheart,
雖然你一直在向我施壓  逼我假裝認識你
Though it seems to be what you're hammering me about.
容我失陪一下
If you'll excuse me,
我要去抽根煙
I need a cigarette.
抽完了我還得去撿
And then I got to remove
掉在我姐姐身上的鋼圜
some of those pennies off of my sister.
那是口棺材  不是什么許愿井
It's a coffin, not a wishing well.
這個葬禮變得好令人感到沉重[沮喪]
This funeral turned out to be very depressing.
沒錯
Well, yeah.
有個死人躺在這里  不死氣沉沉都難
Dead body in the room, generally a buzz-kill.
除非這是愛爾蘭式守靈
Unless it's an Irish wake--
這樣你就可以隔著棺材玩啤酒乒乓啦
then you're playing beer pong off the coffin.
愛爾蘭人愛喝酒  啤酒乒乓是一種喝酒游戲
我的意思是  這家人
No, I mean, how is it possible
怎么可能沒一個人認識我呢
that the family doesn't even know me?
難道安東尼婭從來沒提起過我嗎
Did Antonia never even mention me?
你應該往好的方面想
Let's focus on the positive.
安東尼真的很喜歡你的小屁屁
Anthony really liked your ass.
我知道我和安東尼婭擁有過什么
I know what Antonia and I had.
這就是我們擁有的回憶
This is what we had.
唧唧  唧唧
Peep, peep.
那是我們的美好回憶
That's what we had.
那已經很多啦
Well, that's a lot.
但我猜這家人不會承認我們的回憶
But I guess no one in this family wants to admit that,
這真是太遺憾了
and it's a shame too,
因為我准備了很棒的悼詞
because I had a great eulogy.
是嗎
You do?
是的  沒錯
Yes. I do.
你想讓我跟你分享嗎
Would you like me to share it with you?
當然想啊
I most certainly would.
你不是真的要拿你的爛悼詞
You are not seriously eulogy-bombing
去精神轟炸那位老太太吧
that old lady, are you?
是她先問起我的悼詞的
She asked me about my great eulogy.
她都一百歲了
She's a hundred.
很可能聽成你說你有一位很棒的泌尿科醫生
She probably thought you said you had a great urologist.
你有筆嗎
Do you have a pen?
我要記下她醫生的名字
I'm getting the name of her doctor.
不  夫人  我說的不是"泌尿科醫生"
No, ma'am, I didn't say, "urologist."
我說的是"悼詞"  很棒的悼詞[音似]
I said, "eulogy." A great eulogy.
你憑啥上去念悼詞啊
Why would you give the eulogy?
因為我是卡洛琳﹒錢寧
Because I'm Caroline Channing.
誰呀
Who?
卡洛琳﹒錢寧
Caroline Channing.
安東尼婭是我的保姆
Antonia was my nanny.
我家過去超級有錢
My family was rich,
但后來我父親騙走了全世界的錢
but then my father robbed everyone,
于是我們淪為害群之馬
and we became the scourge of society,
同一周  梅爾﹒吉布森仇視猶太人的言論
overshadowed a little bit by Mel Gibson
蓋過了我家丑聞風頭一點點
hating the Jews that same week.
你們絕對應該記得
Surely, you remember?
小寶貝  我連怎么來這里的都不記得了
Honey, I don't even remember how I got here.
真是難以置信
I can't believe this.
我整個童年之所以"快樂"都是因為
I constructed my entire "Happy" Childhood
我堅信  就算我媽離開了我
On the fact that even though my mom left
就算她不愛我
and apparently didn't love me,
但還有安東尼婭愛我
Antonia did.
而我來了這里  我意識到
And now I get here and I realize
沒人愛過我  她只是為了掙錢
no one loved me, I was just a paycheck.
我只是她照顧的眾多小孩中的一個
One of the many kids she baby-sat.
我甚至不知道我來這里的意義是什么
I don't even know why I bothered to come.
我去一趟洗手間  然后我們就走
I'm going to the restroom and then we can just leave.
打擾一下  你好
Excuse me. Hi.
我是麥克斯  里基的女友
Max, Ricky's girl.
我知道現在你很難過
I know this is a hard time for you,
但對我朋友來說  她也很難過
but it's a hard time for my friend as well.
即使你從來沒有聽說過她
And even though you never heard of her,
但我懇請你能否過去
I was wondering if you could just go over there,
對她說你想起來了
and say you just remembered her,
安東尼婭經常在你們面前提起她
and that Antonia talked about her all the time?
我明白這是要你說謊推翻你之前的話
I know it's a 180 on your original story and a lie,
我也樂意給你辛苦費
and I'd offer to pay you for your trouble,
但我的養老金全在裝著你姐姐的盒子里了
but my 401k is laying in that box on top of your sister.
我是看在你男人里基的面子  才沒趕你倆走
Look, I only permitted you two to stay
要不是去年喬舅舅從樓頂摔下來時
'cause your Ricky was so nice to uncle Joe
全靠他出手相救
when he fell off the roof last year.
但現在  你們還是離開這吧
But now, you gotta go.
好吧  隨便你好了
Okay. Be that way.
但下次喬舅舅要去做透析時  里奇不會去接他的
But don't expect Ricky to pick up Uncle Joe for dialysis.
麥克斯  你這是干什么
Max, what are you doing?
是那家人讓我貼上去的
The family asked me to put it up.
他們想起你來了
They just remembered you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我有這么可悲嗎  需要你粘照片
I'm so pathetic, you have to put up my picture
來哄我嗎
to make me feel better?
在某種程度上  是的
In a way, yes.
這照片本來就應該貼在這里
It belongs up there.
誰不想會認識這個孩子啊
Who wouldn't want to know that kid?
很高興見到你  安東尼婭
Nice to meet you, Antonia.
千萬不要做鬼來找我們
Please don't haunt us.
快上路吧  我們還要買牛肉三明治呢
Now, let's hit the road and get some freaking cheesesteaks!
麥克斯  快把照片弄下來
Max, please take that down.
太丟臉了
It's so embarrassing.
這里沒人認識我
Nobody here knows anything about me.
他們也不認識我啊  小雞仔
They didn't know me either, chicken.
你叫誰小雞仔呢
Hey, who you callin' chicken?
我  那是安東尼婭給我起的昵稱
Me. That was Antonia's nickname for me.
你知道我是誰嗎
You know who I am?
我當然知道
Of course I do.
安東尼婭的小雞仔  她的小唧唧
Antonia's little chick, her peep.
她很愛你
She loved you.
她也喜歡給你做那套裝束
And she loved making you that costume.
整個廚房餐桌上全鋪滿了亮片
Took the whole kitchen table up with all those sequins,
她知道你就該是最耀眼的那一個
But she knew you deserved to sparkle.
她非常愛你  我根本沒辦法抱怨
She loved you so much, I couldn't begin to complain.
不好意思  請問您是哪位
I'm so sorry. What was your name?
我是梅格﹒歐哈拉  我是她的室友
I'm Meg O'Hara. I was her roommate.
兼愛人
And lover.
我們在一起30年了
We were together 30 years.
軍隊拉拉情
The military!
沒錯  明眼人一看就知道了
I know, right? I mean, come on.
當時在坦克那  我的手可是摟著她啊
That's me with my arm around her on that tank.
而那一家子蠢蛋卻還是看不出來
And the family still had no clue.
老一代蕾絲邊  超級酷啊
Vintage lez-- very cool.
安東尼婭會希望你收下這些照片
I know Toni would have wanted you to have these.
感謝你的到來  小雞仔
Oh, thanks for coming, chicken.
你大概是這世界上唯一一個
You're probably the only person in the world
對她的愛像我一樣純粹的人了
who loved her as purely as I did.
麥克斯  看
Max, look.
聖誕節的照片
Christmas.
我生日時的照片
And my birthday.
還有參加青少年選擇獎時的照片
And the Teen Choice Awards.
節哀順變
I'm sorry for your loss.
感激不盡
Thank you.
費城牛肉奶酪三明治  人人有份啦
Philly cheesesteaks for everybody!
我終于活過來了
And you really haven't lived
之前在雪弗蘭里跟九個牛肉三明治
until you've driven two hours in a Chevy
和一只愛放屁的動物待了兩個小時  都要死了
with nine cheesesteaks and a gassy animal.
這有啥  我不就在車上吃完了
What? I ate mine in the car.
厄爾  你錯過了一場精彩的葬禮
Hey, Earl, you missed one hell of a funeral.
你真應該去的
You should have come.
那有不少八九十歲的老辣奶
There were some hot octogenarians,
而且我接收到其中一位超強的"求歡"信號
and I got a definite "jungle fever" vibe from one of them.
像我這種年紀的人  可不想在葬禮上出現
Girl, at my age, you don't go anywhere near funerals.
只要你一不小心打個瞌睡  就得花上六小時
You accidentally doze off, you spend six hours
把你自己從地里挖出來
digging yourself out of the ground.
你還好吧  小雞仔
Hey, how you holding up, chicken?
我沒事  多謝關心
I'm okay. Thanks.
麥克斯  我死的時候
And Max, when I die,
我不在乎我的葬禮都有誰出席
I don't care who else is at my funeral,
只要你來了就行
as long as you're there.
我當然會去
Of course I'll be there.
凶手向來為了甩掉警察而出席葬禮
The murderer always shows up to throw off the cops.
對了  棺材別花太多錢
Also, save the money on a casket
給我一套迪奧壽服  化煙熏妝  扔洞里就行了
and just toss me in a hole wearing Dior and a smoky eye.
如果到時我很胖  那就火葬了吧
Unless I'm fat-- then burn me.
我不想要葬禮
Well, I don't want a funeral.
等我死的時候  把我尸體塞進大炮里
When I die, just shove my corpse into a cannon
直接沖著大西洋城特朗普賭場來一發  送我過去
and blow me directly into the Trump casino.